<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
    <meta type="array">
        <description>CSH for jetts mapping</description>
        <type>CSH</type>
        <csh_table>tx_jetts_mapping</csh_table>
        <fileId>EXT:jetts/locallang_csh_mapping.xml</fileId>
    </meta>
    <data type="array">
        <languageKey index="default" type="array">
            <label index=".description"></label>
            <label index="title.description">Enter a title that describes this template.</label>
            <label index="description.description">Enter a short description for this template.</label>
            <label index="thumbnail.description">Add a thumbnail that will be used in the selectbox as a preview for the template.</label>
            <label index="html.description">The html file that will be used as basis for your template.</label>
            <label index="mapping.description"><![CDATA[Jetts act as a wrapper for the standard TEMPLATE typoscript object. This field allows you to preview what will be passed to this object and learn from it. Use the wizard to generate your mapping.
            
            Don't try to change anything in here, your changes will be overriden on your next save, if you need to add custom Typoscript, use the Override Typoscript field in the advanced tab.]]></label>
            <label index="llxml.description">Jetts can use a standard LLXML file for automatic localisation of your template.
            
            Jetts has already created one file for you in typo3conf/ext/user_jetts_ll, you can use this one as a basis for your template and translate it thanks to llxmltranslate extension.</label>
            <label index="notes.description">This field won't have any effect on your mapping but anything you write here will be available in the "Notes" Panel of the mapping wizard.</label>
            <label index="work_on_subpart.description">In most of the case (99.9%?) you will work on the document body tag. If for any reason you need to start your mapping on a different subpart you can set it here.</label>
            <label index="ts_override.description">If you are not happy with what the wizard has generated for you, you still have a chance to enter you own Typoscript code here. It will be added at the end of the Typoscript generated by the wizard.</label>
        </languageKey>
    </data>
</T3locallang>
