<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
    <meta type="array">
        <description>CSH for jetts mapping</description>
        <type>CSH</type>
        <csh_table>tx_jetts_mapping</csh_table>
        <fileId>EXT:jetts/locallang_csh_mapping.xml</fileId>
    </meta>
    <data type="array">
        <languageKey index="default" type="array">
            <label index=".description"></label>
            <label index="title.description">Enter a title that describes this template.</label>
            <label index="description.description">Enter a short description for this template.</label>
            <label index="thumbnail.description">Add a thumbnail that will be used in the selectbox as a preview for the template.</label>
            <label index="html.description">The html file that will be used as basis for your template.</label>
            <label index="mapping.description">Jetts act as a wrapper for the standard TEMPLATE typoscript object. This field allows you to preview what will be passed to this object and learn from it. Use the wizard to generate your mapping</label>
            <label index="css.description">Select which css files will be included in generated page. These files will be loaded after any css included thanks to typoscript.</label>
            <label index="js.description">Select which js files will be included in generated page. These files will be loaded after any js included thanks to typoscript.</label>
            <label index="js_bottom.description">Select which js files will be loaded at the end of the page. Read this explanation from Yahoo Yslow : "JavaScript scripts block parallel downloads; that is, when a script is downloading, the browser will not start any other downloads. To help the page load faster, move scripts to the bottom of the page if they are deferrable.".</label>
            <label index="llxml.description">Jetts can use a standard LLXML file for automatic localisation of your template. Jetts has already created one file for you in typo3conf/ext/user_jetts_ll, you can use this one as a basis for your template and translate it thanks to llxmltranslate extension.</label>
        </languageKey>
    </data>
</T3locallang>
